<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">VAP</string>
    <string name="strongloop_logo">VAP logo</string>
    <string name="hint_swipe_right_to_left">(Hint: Swipe right-to-left)</string>
    <string name="finale_content"><![CDATA[
        <h3>Credits</h3>
        <p><b>Author</b></br> Alex X. Galloway</p>
           ]]></string>
    <string name="finale_callToAction"><![CDATA[
        <p>For more info on the framework:<p>
        <p><big><strong>
          <a href="mailto:axg105@shsu.edu">axg105@shsu.edu</a>
        </strong></big></p>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="introduction_content"><![CDATA[
        <h3>Welcome to the Video Authentication Protocol Demo!</h3>
        <p>The purpose of the demo is to demonstrate a new model for
        non-repudiation, integrity and authentication of videos.
        This means someone can prove that a video was recorded by their device.</p>
        <p>This occurs in three steps: </p>
        <ol>
        <li>The camera device registers itself with the manufacturer\'s database.</li>
        <li>For every video, the device sends a \"record\" request with metadata to the manufacturer.</li>
        <li>The manufacturer sends a \"confirm\" request to a hardware-protected key store and metadata storage on the camera that sends a reply back.</li>
        </ol>

        <p>In other words, the protocol works by interacting components provided by the device manufacturer.</p>
    <p>    <tt>Video Authentication Server</tt> - This is a remote database owned by the manufacturer that stores video and device metadata.</p>
    <p>    <tt>Video Authentication Client</tt> - The client device with the camera.  This app simulates the function of a hardware chip that communicates to the server.</p>
        <p>Download the Java source code to this app or  NodeJS / MySQL server code at GitHub.</p>
        <p><a href="https://github.com/alexxgathp/vap">Video Authentication Protocol Project</a></p>
    ]]></string>
       <string name="registration_content"><![CDATA[
        <h1>Device Registration</h1>
        <p>Communication is initiated by the device requesting registration and providing required metadata.
        The manufacturer responds by registering the device and its hardware chip, generating a secret device ID and token.
        The manufacturer sends an encrypted communication, with the secret ID and  token, that can only be decrypted by the public key
        on the hardware chip that physically protects it from being accessed by a user.</p>
        <p>If there is no token and ID, the device stores both and sends an encrypted confirmation to the cloud service of the manufacturer.
        The device also sends with each communication an identifier.
        </p>
    ]]></string>
       <string name="android_device_id"><![CDATA[
        <b>Device ID: </b>
    ]]></string>
     <string name="vap_secret_id"><![CDATA[
        <b>VAP Secret ID: </b>
    ]]></string>
     <string name="vap_token"><![CDATA[
        <b>VAP Token: </b>
    ]]></string>
       <string name="vap_old_token"><![CDATA[
        <b>VAP Previous Token: </b>
    ]]></string>
     <string name="privatekey"><![CDATA[
        <b>Private Key: </b>
    ]]></string>
     <string name="metadata"><![CDATA[
        <b>Metadata: </b>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="lessonOne_content"><![CDATA[
        <h3>Demo One: VAP request.</h3>
        <p> A VAP request is a request to authenticate a video. The simulation is broken up into three level of granularity,
        assuming a video is recorded and their is a metadata file, assuming a video is recorded and metadata needs to be retrieved still,
        and the full real world situation, assuming no video is recorded yet. Ideally, VAP requests are built-in to the video recording process.
        For the first, a metadata J3M file must be exported by <a href="https://guardianproject.info/informa/">Informacam</a> and a video to the test server.</p>
        <p>In a complete prototype of the framework, a video\'s
         metadata will be generated automatically, request to be recorded and verified by device manufacturer\'s datacenter.</p>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="lessonOne_user">User</string>
    <string name="lessonOne_user_hint">Me</string>
    <string name="lessonOne_comment">Comment</string>
    <string name="lessonOne_editComment_hint">My comment</string>
    <string name="lessonOne_reviewed">Reviewed</string>
    <string name="send_request">Send Request</string>
    <string name="lessonTwo_content"><![CDATA[
        <h3>Demo Two: Manufacturer\'s Database.</h3>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="lessonThree_content"><![CDATA[
        <h3>Lesson Three: Don\'t Outgrow, Outbuild.</h3>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="warning_mapsNotAvailable">
        Your device does not support Google Maps.
        Locations will be displayed in a list. To get an interactive map view,
        use a real device supporting OpenGL ES 2.0. Any model made after 2010 should be fine.</string>
    <string name="title_front_page">Video Authentication Protocol</string>
    <string name="record_video_button">Record a Video</string>
    <string name="select_video_button">Select a Video</string>
    <string name="select_metadata_button">Select J3M File</string>
    <string name="device_button">See the Devices</string>
    <string name="video_button">See the Videos</string>

<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="this_android_device_label">This Android Device</string>
    <string name="title_activity_item_details">ItemDetails</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="simulate_video_upload">2. Simulate By Video Upload (Under Development)</string>
    <string name="simulate_j3m">1. Simulate With Informacam J3M</string>
    <string name="simulate_take_video">3.  Simulate By Recording Video (Under Development)</string>
    <string name="error_package_error">There was an error with the activity\'s package.</string>
    <string name="error_in_development">This feature is not fully implemented yet.</string>
</resources>
